Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4172
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
1970- 1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Miller, J. Gormly
Harper, Shirley
/4172
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
3108953
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 05, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4108: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4139: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files /4145: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4156: ILR School Librarian's Office Additional Files /4169: Martin P. Catherwood Library Librarian's Office Additional Files
Harper, Shirley F.; Miller, J. Gormly; Martin P. Catherwood Library. Librarian's Office; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
3108953
- Budget - 1970 and prior (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Budget - 1970/71, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Budget - 1971/72, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Budget - 1972/73, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Budget - 1973/74, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Budget - 1974/75, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Budget - 1975/1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Budget - 1976/77, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Budget - 1977/78, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Budget - 1978/79, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Budget - 1979/80, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Budget 1980/81, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Budget 1981/82, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Budget 1982/1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Budget 1983/1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Budget 1984/1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Budget 1985/1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Budget 1986/87, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Budget: Library Automation Project 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Fiscal: Guide LMDC (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Fiscal: Hatfield FND. Endowment for Econ. Education (11783) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Fiscal: ILR Title II C Retroactive Conversion Project (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Fiscal: Japanese - US Friendship Comm. Grant (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Fiscal Memoranda (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Fiscal Statements and Reports (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Fiscal Years: 1986-87, 1988-89, 1989-90, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Fiscal Years: 1982-83, 1983-84, 1984-85, 1985-86, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Fiscal Years: 1978-79, 1979-80, 1980-81, 1981-82, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Fiscal Years: 1975-76, 1976-77, 1977-78, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Student Assistants (1968-73), 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Student Assistants - Inactive 75-78 Part 1, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Student Assistants - Inactive 75-78 Part 2, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Student Assistants - Inactive 75-78 Part 3, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Student Assistants - Inactive 75-78 Part 4, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Cornell Non-Academic Employees Part 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Cornell Non-Academic Employees Part 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Cornell Non-Academic Employees Part 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Inactive Student Assistants 81-82 Part 1, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Inactive Student Assistants 81-82 Part 1, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Inactive Student Assistants 83-84 Part 1, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Inactive Student Assistants 83-84 Part 2, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Inactive Student Assistants 80-85, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Inactive Student Assistants 85-86 Part 1, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Inactive Student Assistants 85-86 Part 2, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Inactive Student Assistants 87-88 Part 1, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Inactive Student Assistants 87-88 Part 2, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Inactive Student Assistants 89 Part 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Inactive Student Assistants 89 Part 2, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)